{
  "1": {
    "question": "4003003310200040344001003",
    "answer": "4443343313223443344131333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "0102003001003030000003001",
    "answer": "2142223441133433443333441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "1002000301013000301030001",
    "answer": "1432244341413443341434441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "0210002002003320100022022",
    "answer": "4214442442433324144422422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "0032000014030301400004200",
    "answer": "3332244414433341441444224",
    "size": 5
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "4300002200000000042000014",
    "answer": "4333142214441242242444414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "0102020013000000320240012",
    "answer": "2122323413434434324244212",
    "size": 5
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "1200003024000004303000043",
    "answer": "1224443124434244343341443",
    "size": 5
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "0102100000310210000041030",
    "answer": "3122134444312214443241332",
    "size": 5
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "0420100100100100030004121",
    "answer": "4422144144133144432444121",
    "size": 5
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "2233003002000002003001232",
    "answer": "2233333422344312423221232",
    "size": 5
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "2030020001133300001010300",
    "answer": "2433324441133324441214333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "0000313000033000012402010",
    "answer": "4443313434433244412442214",
    "size": 5
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "0004000230030203000310220",
    "answer": "4444312233334223443314223",
    "size": 5
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "0210010000012400000300330",
    "answer": "2212214443412434421343331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "1021200000120104033000000",
    "answer": "1221244442122144433444344",
    "size": 5
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "2000001330101000203000130",
    "answer": "2444421333121443233433134",
    "size": 5
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "2100000202303000030000013",
    "answer": "2124224242343433434334313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "3002003014020200202003030",
    "answer": "3342243414424244242443334",
    "size": 5
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "0121000230030100120003340",
    "answer": "4121343233433144122433344",
    "size": 5
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "0130330001003224001000000",
    "answer": "3133334441343224331344433",
    "size": 5
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "0000031201302300000220220",
    "answer": "3444431231342322443224221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "2301004020000000201002033",
    "answer": "2331424324344243241432333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "1320000310002000310000313",
    "answer": "1322443314422444313343313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "0210000300000300001032032",
    "answer": "2214444334344343231232332",
    "size": 5
  },
  "26": {
    "question": "0040212002010302003410100",
    "answer": "4444212232214342443414144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "27": {
    "question": "0033042020010400304202400",
    "answer": "4233342122413414334222442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "28": {
    "question": "2000320021001001300300010",
    "answer": "2433324221441431344333413",
    "size": 5
  },
  "29": {
    "question": "2030100100000200210110000",
    "answer": "2334123144444244212112333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "30": {
    "question": "2002003001301200000004210",
    "answer": "2442223441331224423344213",
    "size": 5
  },
  "31": {
    "question": "1021000030201000203000120",
    "answer": "1321423234231343223433122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "32": {
    "question": "1002001300002010120230010",
    "answer": "1332241344442414124233312",
    "size": 5
  },
  "33": {
    "question": "0200240002030001023000043",
    "answer": "4224244342433441223344443",
    "size": 5
  },
  "34": {
    "question": "3100000100100210100300100",
    "answer": "3144433124144213144333133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "35": {
    "question": "0002330103300011020222000",
    "answer": "3422334133342411424222442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "36": {
    "question": "1000230100020100300002100",
    "answer": "1444233142322141333422144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "37": {
    "question": "0300000212003012130000002",
    "answer": "4333242212443312134224442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "38": {
    "question": "3201003000001220100000330",
    "answer": "3221433444441224144443334",
    "size": 5
  },
  "39": {
    "question": "3000000210430300100102200",
    "answer": "3334442214433344144142244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "40": {
    "question": "2204103020000000202044021",
    "answer": "2244133422324334212344421",
    "size": 5
  },
  "41": {
    "question": "0124103040000000302022330",
    "answer": "4124143242434424322122333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "42": {
    "question": "1000022301040104023200001",
    "answer": "1444422331443124223241331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "43": {
    "question": "0001000203301030000021031",
    "answer": "3421334243341432434421331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "44": {
    "question": "1000002300430230013000002",
    "answer": "1244442324433234413333322",
    "size": 5
  },
  "45": {
    "question": "2030120000332130000320403",
    "answer": "2333124444332132324324443",
    "size": 5
  },
  "46": {
    "question": "4030100023013003000001021",
    "answer": "4432144323313433444331221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "47": {
    "question": "0000210010230210400230000",
    "answer": "4444213312232212444233342",
    "size": 5
  },
  "48": {
    "question": "0041000202000003020004300",
    "answer": "4441242232344333422134333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "49": {
    "question": "3032000041020102400004401",
    "answer": "3332244441122132413324441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "50": {
    "question": "3020440001000004000220301",
    "answer": "3324443241441424131222331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "51": {
    "question": "0130003100000201000002310",
    "answer": "3133333124444241433422314",
    "size": 5
  },
  "52": {
    "question": "0000203001031020141002000",
    "answer": "4342243441431424141222444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "53": {
    "question": "0012002030030300402002100",
    "answer": "1212232334334344442422124",
    "size": 5
  },
  "54": {
    "question": "0000020331040402120100000",
    "answer": "2444423331144442122124444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "55": {
    "question": "0201001400200010013002040",
    "answer": "1221221432244311413422444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "56": {
    "question": "0300003130430320143000040",
    "answer": "4344443134434324143222441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "57": {
    "question": "2000101012001302100100000",
    "answer": "2233131312331322133124444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "58": {
    "question": "1013102000030300302000020",
    "answer": "1213142434434344342443424",
    "size": 5
  },
  "59": {
    "question": "0210001020030100210000031",
    "answer": "2212441324433144213442331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "60": {
    "question": "3000001001023201212000010",
    "answer": "3444431331323231212333313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "61": {
    "question": "3203001303000001031004041",
    "answer": "3223331343323441231444441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "62": {
    "question": "1010100300200100010031033",
    "answer": "1413124334244143314431333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "63": {
    "question": "2100304401000002031020041",
    "answer": "2133324441133422431224441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "64": {
    "question": "0000001031302002003020100",
    "answer": "3444431231342342443424144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "65": {
    "question": "0212010301200030012003000",
    "answer": "2212213331244432412333323",
    "size": 5
  },
  "66": {
    "question": "0240102030030300403010410",
    "answer": "1244132434334344413414414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "67": {
    "question": "1024000200030313000010032",
    "answer": "1424444244434313343214432",
    "size": 5
  },
  "68": {
    "question": "0030300001313422000040400",
    "answer": "3133334441313422233244441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "69": {
    "question": "1200203000100300200140020",
    "answer": "1224233442134334223144422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "70": {
    "question": "1301400000200030000043013",
    "answer": "1331423444241234432343313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "71": {
    "question": "0010200002430100220000010",
    "answer": "4314243442434144224433314",
    "size": 5
  },
  "72": {
    "question": "0010002301010032040030000",
    "answer": "3212232331313432244333343",
    "size": 5
  },
  "73": {
    "question": "0100120032303003033001000",
    "answer": "2133124432343123433431444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "74": {
    "question": "0021031003200023001203200",
    "answer": "3321331233224423441233221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "75": {
    "question": "3002233030020300302131003",
    "answer": "3442233431224333322131333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "76": {
    "question": "0013003000000202302010204",
    "answer": "2213313443234242342412244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "77": {
    "question": "1010400030210340300020301",
    "answer": "1413424434214341332422321",
    "size": 5
  },
  "78": {
    "question": "1410440302000003020330233",
    "answer": "1414444342433423121333233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "79": {
    "question": "2003000100000343000220100",
    "answer": "2333424144344343343222132",
    "size": 5
  },
  "80": {
    "question": "0000203012302300030010100",
    "answer": "4444233212342344433414144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "81": {
    "question": "0030110032013000003001000",
    "answer": "4433114432413124433441444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "82": {
    "question": "0000031201000100220310003",
    "answer": "3323331231444134224314443",
    "size": 5
  },
  "83": {
    "question": "4000012130000000023001000",
    "answer": "4444312133424444423441233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "84": {
    "question": "0000012120000103003000301",
    "answer": "3332412124324143443434331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "85": {
    "question": "0022303443000001324022100",
    "answer": "4422343443432431324122122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "86": {
    "question": "0102030010100024100300002",
    "answer": "3122133412144424133344422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "87": {
    "question": "0020014000313000001001001",
    "answer": "4422414434313343441431441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "88": {
    "question": "0003102010010200302014000",
    "answer": "4333142213413234332314444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "89": {
    "question": "1010030010200310000000212",
    "answer": "1313333413244312433212212",
    "size": 5
  },
  "90": {
    "question": "0200001022000300202201400",
    "answer": "2244441422423334242241444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "91": {
    "question": "0042002030000010003013001",
    "answer": "4442242333124413343313431",
    "size": 5
  },
  "92": {
    "question": "0000131333000002333110000",
    "answer": "3322131333244442333114444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "93": {
    "question": "3022030034002004100404404",
    "answer": "3422134434342344123444414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "94": {
    "question": "0300100340210210330040010",
    "answer": "1344123344212214333244412",
    "size": 5
  },
  "95": {
    "question": "0102404100030200041014040",
    "answer": "4122444144432243341214442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "96": {
    "question": "0300122002101000000102103",
    "answer": "3334122442141424443122133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "97": {
    "question": "0020040103002032041000022",
    "answer": "4224444143422432441324422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "98": {
    "question": "3020000014310244400000301",
    "answer": "3422434414314244432444331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "99": {
    "question": "0132000010100032001013001",
    "answer": "2132223313144432241313331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "100": {
    "question": "1000302010010200210010040",
    "answer": "1244332413314233212412444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "101": {
    "question": "0100200240100010140030040",
    "answer": "4144244242142413142233444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "102": {
    "question": "3200100330000000240030024",
    "answer": "3223134334344142242433324",
    "size": 5
  },
  "103": {
    "question": "0201301000400000310122003",
    "answer": "4221341443433434314122333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "104": {
    "question": "2010130000320130000320101",
    "answer": "2214134443322133444322141",
    "size": 5
  },
  "105": {
    "question": "0020003004410423003000300",
    "answer": "4422443344413423313231331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "106": {
    "question": "1240240010000000400330322",
    "answer": "1244242412414314413333322",
    "size": 5
  },
  "107": {
    "question": "0013004200000303012000021",
    "answer": "4413444234332343412444421",
    "size": 5
  },
  "108": {
    "question": "3020000102000120120020100",
    "answer": "3223333132444124122322133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "109": {
    "question": "0200110323303000020000200",
    "answer": "2232114323343433424334244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "110": {
    "question": "3100000034310312300000041",
    "answer": "3144432234313312344423341",
    "size": 5
  },
  "111": {
    "question": "1203000330201003001300100",
    "answer": "1223424334241443441333133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "112": {
    "question": "1200002003010300321000000",
    "answer": "1244442433412344321443344",
    "size": 5
  },
  "113": {
    "question": "0000121020023000003001001",
    "answer": "2333121224323443233431221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "114": {
    "question": "2010220001013000300012010",
    "answer": "2412224441313333344412214",
    "size": 5
  },
  "115": {
    "question": "0120120030001203002001010",
    "answer": "2122123334341243442431414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "116": {
    "question": "1300000103030330100000301",
    "answer": "1344443143434334144443331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "117": {
    "question": "0100032134000100000012030",
    "answer": "3133432134324144443412233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "118": {
    "question": "3200400000320120000020034",
    "answer": "3224431442322122144423334",
    "size": 5
  },
  "119": {
    "question": "2300100000133200001040100",
    "answer": "2333124444133224431344133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "120": {
    "question": "2000023002010033223100000",
    "answer": "2334223442314333223134444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "121": {
    "question": "0000132023300031204430000",
    "answer": "3242132423344331224433344",
    "size": 5
  },
  "122": {
    "question": "0303002440400030122002040",
    "answer": "4333442444423334122422444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "123": {
    "question": "2000100300100000320202041",
    "answer": "2444124333132423324222441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "124": {
    "question": "1301000200010120010010200",
    "answer": "1331343233412124413212233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "125": {
    "question": "2000321200030100030000140",
    "answer": "2444321243432134334444144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "126": {
    "question": "2212000301020000210230302",
    "answer": "2212244331423444214233342",
    "size": 5
  },
  "127": {
    "question": "0300032010210330404100030",
    "answer": "3344432214213332444114333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "128": {
    "question": "0100000230102040043001200",
    "answer": "2133424234142442443321223",
    "size": 5
  },
  "129": {
    "question": "1200300100002030100140120",
    "answer": "1224333143432434124144122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "130": {
    "question": "0012120400020300000001020",
    "answer": "2412124424324343233431224",
    "size": 5
  },
  "131": {
    "question": "0103000002130314000003010",
    "answer": "4133344422133314444233312",
    "size": 5
  },
  "132": {
    "question": "0030000012313010000201000",
    "answer": "4333244412313313443231442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "133": {
    "question": "1000301010042400304010001",
    "answer": "1444341413442434324413341",
    "size": 5
  },
  "134": {
    "question": "0403310003012000010022031",
    "answer": "4443314243312443313422331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "135": {
    "question": "0000000210004000320204201",
    "answer": "2123323213434424324244241",
    "size": 5
  },
  "136": {
    "question": "1000000201303200000020020",
    "answer": "1423334231343223433122122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "137": {
    "question": "1020020130030300103030001",
    "answer": "1322423134234343143433441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "138": {
    "question": "3300000020423440400000014",
    "answer": "3344432422423444433442214",
    "size": 5
  },
  "139": {
    "question": "0023403000030300001012400",
    "answer": "4323443234434344241412441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "140": {
    "question": "1001003100004200001021201",
    "answer": "1221433124344242441421221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "141": {
    "question": "3000101020003300030001200",
    "answer": "3444131422343344434441224",
    "size": 5
  },
  "142": {
    "question": "3001000220030400102010000",
    "answer": "3331444224433444132214444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "143": {
    "question": "0000221302100100200000220",
    "answer": "2444221342123143234433224",
    "size": 5
  },
  "144": {
    "question": "2230200002130213000030133",
    "answer": "2233233432134213442333133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "145": {
    "question": "2120100310100000021300100",
    "answer": "2122123314134443221333133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "146": {
    "question": "0010001020104100024003000",
    "answer": "3312331423144133424433244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "147": {
    "question": "3210000020000010200303010",
    "answer": "3213332423344212243333313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "148": {
    "question": "0003101024100000101000300",
    "answer": "2333121424144242141423334",
    "size": 5
  },
  "149": {
    "question": "1003002022000003201004003",
    "answer": "1233332422344433221344443",
    "size": 5
  },
  "150": {
    "question": "0102032100000000043103040",
    "answer": "3122432144323341343133444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "151": {
    "question": "2130000002040201000000141",
    "answer": "2133224432442211344433141",
    "size": 5
  },
  "152": {
    "question": "0102000104010304020001030",
    "answer": "3122433134413344422441333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "153": {
    "question": "0100200304021200200010001",
    "answer": "4132243344421244242414441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "154": {
    "question": "4200102103000000031001001",
    "answer": "4244142143443432331321221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "155": {
    "question": "0003002203301000001031020",
    "answer": "4443342243341443441431422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "156": {
    "question": "3100000012013304200000012",
    "answer": "3144234412313314223244412",
    "size": 5
  },
  "157": {
    "question": "0300240100100040020440020",
    "answer": "4333244142142444121444422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "158": {
    "question": "1003000022210001223200010",
    "answer": "1433324422214331223233312",
    "size": 5
  },
  "159": {
    "question": "0002220310040000312201000",
    "answer": "2332224313444333312231333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "160": {
    "question": "0300112000020100002310040",
    "answer": "3334112443324133322314444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "161": {
    "question": "3000001210300020030103000",
    "answer": "3444431212342424434143344",
    "size": 5
  },
  "162": {
    "question": "0202102000040300002024010",
    "answer": "3212132324343342422424414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "163": {
    "question": "0020020010102300400002201",
    "answer": "2322423314122344443442231",
    "size": 5
  },
  "164": {
    "question": "0030030331040104120300400",
    "answer": "3432234331344134122344413",
    "size": 5
  },
  "165": {
    "question": "1001000130010002023010001",
    "answer": "1441444134212342423414441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "166": {
    "question": "1010000000010213021004000",
    "answer": "1413334423314213221244442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "167": {
    "question": "0100140310030400120420040",
    "answer": "4122143312432424124422141",
    "size": 5
  },
  "168": {
    "question": "3200200030302010100020031",
    "answer": "3223231332322412144423331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "169": {
    "question": "0200423100000100003010102",
    "answer": "1224423144233134443314122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "170": {
    "question": "2000300100300100000223002",
    "answer": "2444323143334132444223332",
    "size": 5
  },
  "171": {
    "question": "4001002300002000033001004",
    "answer": "4231242332442212333421444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "172": {
    "question": "2000100202340122030020002",
    "answer": "2233133232342122433324422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "173": {
    "question": "2000003103200300000200210",
    "answer": "2244433143234332444212212",
    "size": 5
  },
  "174": {
    "question": "2000300010310300030010100",
    "answer": "2243334413314343233412144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "175": {
    "question": "3000030223010401320200002",
    "answer": "3444334223314431324233242",
    "size": 5
  },
  "176": {
    "question": "0230010002030100030010204",
    "answer": "2233314442234122334412244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "177": {
    "question": "2040003003043204001000102",
    "answer": "2444423323143234441322122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "178": {
    "question": "0021223400000030022000010",
    "answer": "1221223442234434322344413",
    "size": 5
  },
  "179": {
    "question": "1030000024001203003112200",
    "answer": "1334434324341243443112233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "180": {
    "question": "1003100300030002001002230",
    "answer": "1443144334234442331312233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "181": {
    "question": "1031003000020000002310301",
    "answer": "1331443444422334432313321",
    "size": 5
  },
  "182": {
    "question": "0201000030210301003003120",
    "answer": "1221424434214341343433122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "183": {
    "question": "3300002042003002301000022",
    "answer": "3331212242233442341444422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "184": {
    "question": "0003120032000100210101000",
    "answer": "2433124432324123214131444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "185": {
    "question": "1000120230032011000200001",
    "answer": "1444124233232311332244441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "186": {
    "question": "0001030330003002120100000",
    "answer": "3441434334343442122124444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "187": {
    "question": "3000040102003000332220000",
    "answer": "3334244142443442332224444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "188": {
    "question": "3201000024200003100000003",
    "answer": "3221433424224243143433433",
    "size": 5
  },
  "189": {
    "question": "1220000103032000000313130",
    "answer": "1223344143432444324313133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "190": {
    "question": "0020020000303230010140000",
    "answer": "2422324443333234412144333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "191": {
    "question": "2000314401044006350000000031403503010050440004104",
    "answer": "2233314461544446356664635631463563316656444444144",
    "size": 7
  },
  "192": {
    "question": "2004440050600000005120040301425003003040060000010",
    "answer": "2664444256666245555124244331425463643546663355516",
    "size": 7
  },
  "193": {
    "question": "0003030402120546302054000001103046450226040505000",
    "answer": "4623335462125546342554634661163446456226645555644",
    "size": 7
  },
  "194": {
    "question": "0020000000014010050602050101355601000000230000050",
    "answer": "6224446666614616556662256161355661336662233555553",
    "size": 7
  },
  "195": {
    "question": "0004001023143033500100400040040054504432405001000",
    "answer": "1334431223143333554153415545543354554432455551245",
    "size": 7
  },
  "196": {
    "question": "0400330020044003150050102020400152003300300140010",
    "answer": "4443335422444533155453122525443152543345334144413",
    "size": 7
  },
  "197": {
    "question": "0030240102005000203600000000050200035020032005002",
    "answer": "3332244162555466253643665363356236335526632255622",
    "size": 7
  },
  "198": {
    "question": "0050201000206300314004600000403100040100041000005",
    "answer": "5555221562246346314634634463463166646144441655555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "199": {
    "question": "6000001540050004103300300040031012000600611000005",
    "answer": "6666661544455554133355334445531412256666611655555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "200": {
    "question": "3040000342033004400300060100020032006606160000501",
    "answer": "3344446342233644466366666126223332666666166555551",
    "size": 7
  },
  "201": {
    "question": "2200500544402104030350004000560204053013350020015",
    "answer": "2255555544422154633355664445566224553613353322315",
    "size": 7
  },
  "202": {
    "question": "3400310300420200010560100050240600030440050310055",
    "answer": "3433312344425236612562166556246656634446653315555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "203": {
    "question": "3003100301301500000206330335040000034035010033005",
    "answer": "3223155331331566662256336335343132234435513433555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "204": {
    "question": "2000000033301301000000022400201050021026000001300",
    "answer": "2555533233351341444564422456241555621226663331333",
    "size": 7
  },
  "205": {
    "question": "3200005000006542505030010500406051366000004000031",
    "answer": "3225555336666542555634216563446651366613224444331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "206": {
    "question": "0000050000500000002602650205310012100005000400600",
    "answer": "5556655665566526662652655265314512134455263466666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "207": {
    "question": "0150001623002000010010510400004000100030100015000",
    "answer": "6155551623352262316616514466654466165333155515555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "208": {
    "question": "4100014020204002021240040400005000004044000060226",
    "answer": "4155514425254442421244544426655556664444666666226",
    "size": 7
  },
  "209": {
    "question": "4133310000004644220400600040012004000300105513004",
    "answer": "4133316455554644225466666646512264655334165513444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "210": {
    "question": "4000003610300003003010000260034023200000030450005",
    "answer": "4446633614366363633616366262634623264466336455555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "211": {
    "question": "3144200000045030001540230650563000206600000066333",
    "answer": "3144224366445432661545236654563325256662525566333",
    "size": 7
  },
  "212": {
    "question": "3033310300555036500600013300030066503630050221305",
    "answer": "3633316365555636566666613335636666533633651221355",
    "size": 7
  },
  "213": {
    "question": "4006000444030000000121000130000004030020101540000",
    "answer": "4666666444333266666121654133335444335522121544442",
    "size": 7
  },
  "214": {
    "question": "1412000200650020400046004005300060200420020001441",
    "answer": "1412244246655424466546614655364464236422423661441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "215": {
    "question": "0030301106503004050400405040500060204022010330120",
    "answer": "3335331166563454656445465642546566254622615333122",
    "size": 7
  },
  "216": {
    "question": "3505504300600432555001200501531051303000030002213",
    "answer": "3555544356666432555641266561531651353366635552213",
    "size": 7
  },
  "217": {
    "question": "0303120600040005554222000000050105140005560100000",
    "answer": "6333122666644465554222566666256155144455564166666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "218": {
    "question": "1031000230330205030105000025106402000433101000300",
    "answer": "1331444235334225534125566425166442566433151444355",
    "size": 7
  },
  "219": {
    "question": "2002200000000300400053460004003020140100200001401",
    "answer": "2262233346655334465553466444133224143144224441441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "220": {
    "question": "0002600050030064044300033010040310304060020033002",
    "answer": "5522666655433664544366433416646313364666326333662",
    "size": 7
  },
  "221": {
    "question": "2030040000604100440030450160600230033010000300404",
    "answer": "2233444663664164446636452163665236333513341355444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "222": {
    "question": "0001006033000200533003006000013332200000060220400",
    "answer": "5131666533666255533323666666313332236666661224444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "223": {
    "question": "0003440303042334000204400044050005423604040344000",
    "answer": "3133443343442334556234456644255655423664543344455",
    "size": 7
  },
  "224": {
    "question": "0005333050155541440004060405000163144460304333000",
    "answer": "4555333455155541444254666425666163144466334333666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "225": {
    "question": "1200224023000041403340040300000402120100500000031",
    "answer": "1233224423555441453344545324454452125155552553331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "226": {
    "question": "0026101000024013302000600060003056101500003036600",
    "answer": "6226141666624413332426666562633356161555623336662",
    "size": 7
  },
  "227": {
    "question": "5000056023320040000000101000002333040000506001201",
    "answer": "5555256523325642355564121666462333546655556661221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "228": {
    "question": "0006000100003032001010050000154100000060000000504",
    "answer": "6666661125553332561313356654154165455466545544554",
    "size": 7
  },
  "229": {
    "question": "0015050300060530051000330640004100440500040303500",
    "answer": "3515555356666535551661333644444166445555641333566",
    "size": 7
  },
  "230": {
    "question": "2212210400060001550040304010400453000200020442231",
    "answer": "2212214466666441555644334514432453214244324442231",
    "size": 7
  },
  "231": {
    "question": "2300100000004500154006100404542000000000600000000",
    "answer": "2333155266644566154556125464542556454445645556664",
    "size": 7
  },
  "232": {
    "question": "0230000013322330600033030203400010444412200000140",
    "answer": "2234444313322332666633232263413316444412241333144",
    "size": 7
  },
  "233": {
    "question": "0040000004001600641000500500033303406000500202201",
    "answer": "5646666564461656641345566534633353466665542262251",
    "size": 7
  },
  "234": {
    "question": "3100010050515002050200305020010403003440300200031",
    "answer": "3133315355515532256251335625313463233446322246631",
    "size": 7
  },
  "235": {
    "question": "1010203003044003300040050000214000204051030000601",
    "answer": "1412233443644343366442555662214563244451336666661",
    "size": 7
  },
  "236": {
    "question": "0030301105040060015020305002032032010201000000510",
    "answer": "5533341155544466615526365552632332313231235555513",
    "size": 7
  },
  "237": {
    "question": "0002001504100004000200400040102006030504011200102",
    "answer": "5522661544162654666265425446132546633554611225122",
    "size": 7
  },
  "238": {
    "question": "5055500100020021063400030300031504600500030021203",
    "answer": "5555566166622621663462336346131534655552431221233",
    "size": 7
  },
  "239": {
    "question": "0605000050240005330420000000220323000630200002020",
    "answer": "6665555652244565333426555242226323366633236622121",
    "size": 7
  },
  "240": {
    "question": "4044005000603502213300000000063332043050001001303",
    "answer": "4444655666663542213354666665463332243555551331333",
    "size": 7
  },
  "241": {
    "question": "0041200033344000000006143410000032210000060030030",
    "answer": "4441225433344566664556143415644332214666663336333",
    "size": 7
  },
  "242": {
    "question": "0514042000000050505240603020135010400000001602230",
    "answer": "5514442566664256555245653324135314433666631662233",
    "size": 7
  },
  "243": {
    "question": "1000000010350200330050100265004060600100101204300",
    "answer": "1666662616355266332556144265644666662144161244333",
    "size": 7
  },
  "244": {
    "question": "0050415630200003021300304000020200030100000000001",
    "answer": "6654415635244563521356354435625243532124663366661",
    "size": 7
  },
  "245": {
    "question": "0040042006000040333442000140440003000610050020101",
    "answer": "4644442466666244333442266144446333546615554622151",
    "size": 7
  },
  "246": {
    "question": "0002000010533000350602315000064052000040130003301",
    "answer": "6662236616533663356662315623264552366444136663331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "247": {
    "question": "4003100004500000005051000500301056100303032005030",
    "answer": "4333155444566566655651366565331656125333632555533",
    "size": 7
  },
  "248": {
    "question": "0040000604620020402020043134022000005000503060000",
    "answer": "6646666664623226462322643134322334435555543666666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "249": {
    "question": "0352201600060403401600000000054055050300055033250",
    "answer": "6352261635566463451646645664654455455312555533251",
    "size": 7
  },
  "250": {
    "question": "0001033430000330000505200020010510004000000060050",
    "answer": "4441633436666333655515225225514516554446655566655",
    "size": 7
  },
  "251": {
    "question": "2204600030043000302000420230002040005500100042031",
    "answer": "2244666433443644312365424236552444245523124442331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "252": {
    "question": "3100501023305602304000040500002035056013505050051",
    "answer": "3155551323315632344666644556662235656613565555351",
    "size": 7
  },
  "253": {
    "question": "0000520250001000006040120000604041004033200460000",
    "answer": "2555522256661466246646124464644341464633226466666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "254": {
    "question": "3040160000400035641006500012005524400060000330103",
    "answer": "3644166366466635641626566212655524466664431333133",
    "size": 7
  },
  "255": {
    "question": "2330522210005550630220300010530360655000463330241",
    "answer": "2333522216655553635225363616536366655644463332241",
    "size": 7
  },
  "256": {
    "question": "0000403000005000102020204060030220063050001010101",
    "answer": "6444433655555362122626244662634226663455561315151",
    "size": 7
  },
  "257": {
    "question": "2000040500000020000460000000000402500006021500050",
    "answer": "2244446555666625444462515555444422566666621555552",
    "size": 7
  },
  "258": {
    "question": "2003050440334040000000303001602100503140000004040",
    "answer": "2253555445334544555456323341632134563145556664445",
    "size": 7
  },
  "259": {
    "question": "6000005044105000302655005005533010003062204000001",
    "answer": "6666665444125543332655555665533616643662264446661",
    "size": 7
  },
  "260": {
    "question": "4400041004160000100460564240450020000644004500021",
    "answer": "4466641244164625166464564246456426645644264566621",
    "size": 7
  },
  "261": {
    "question": "2030013000200000600000004261040404000036003230100",
    "answer": "2336613232266346662634464261346444632636663233166",
    "size": 7
  },
  "262": {
    "question": "1500063305500000005030404500505000560000004000034",
    "answer": "1556663335566353545635444555555664566663444444334",
    "size": 7
  },
  "263": {
    "question": "3006200150040040504104000006000100341032331000060",
    "answer": "3336226156644645564164566466453126341332331666666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "264": {
    "question": "0500000050416064006500204050024005301450500000050",
    "answer": "6555566654416664466566214656624465361456535555653",
    "size": 7
  },
  "265": {
    "question": "0300050003101010420020200301610033005000000002000",
    "answer": "2355555233141212424426242341614433465555546662244",
    "size": 7
  },
  "266": {
    "question": "2444344260400450051000005000005500450010551233555",
    "answer": "2444344266433455651245665521565544452314551233555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "267": {
    "question": "0151004200022002206300000003035040440030301300001",
    "answer": "2151444255522442256334666663435544443533341355221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "268": {
    "question": "4200206013023005000000500050000003004502503040055",
    "answer": "4221266413523645353364535556355333634522553444555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "269": {
    "question": "5020100000500201013022600360030130100300000006004",
    "answer": "5522155556555251613622666366236136163364666666444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "270": {
    "question": "2003550010000544040001330262000101240000600355005",
    "answer": "2333555216666544442651333262444161243666663355555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "271": {
    "question": "0120004440332003000203505053050006005550556000550",
    "answer": "4122444444332433553233565553656666365556556666555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "272": {
    "question": "4003220000040033300000100640004410604600335001003",
    "answer": "4333226444644633366465166646544416654666335561663",
    "size": 7
  },
  "273": {
    "question": "4040001105000030602031005002305040200003043000402",
    "answer": "4444551135553333662231665552365544236333443444422",
    "size": 7
  },
  "274": {
    "question": "0000260543050055405000200050004065100405150220000",
    "answer": "4442266543356655435565246656524665133465153226555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "275": {
    "question": "1005000401224340006440055600422000113331030005005",
    "answer": "1555533451224346666444555664422553113331332255555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "276": {
    "question": "0435021040501404050400105060060102044040405505540",
    "answer": "4435221643561464356446155664666162244446445555544",
    "size": 7
  },
  "277": {
    "question": "0003021250203310010630000200414404000000310122003",
    "answer": "2333221252263315516634552266414444645555314122533",
    "size": 7
  },
  "278": {
    "question": "0262040500010500040000001320001002001004000602000",
    "answer": "2262244566414556443455641325561632551664456662244",
    "size": 7
  },
  "279": {
    "question": "5550500006003003032004020101003405001005000010133",
    "answer": "5555522666663363332234422151433445541345532214133",
    "size": 7
  },
  "280": {
    "question": "2030012505010050000462020000002100000005013015540",
    "answer": "2233312555514256644462626666262154636655413315544",
    "size": 7
  },
  "281": {
    "question": "3134004050100000065006500056001300000030406004441",
    "answer": "3134444353156635365566566656651365665336466664441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "282": {
    "question": "0050512020030010300502234353010050300600303440400",
    "answer": "5555512224435213343532234353316655336666313444433",
    "size": 7
  },
  "283": {
    "question": "1003200060121002000066250333200006006660300024004",
    "answer": "1333266666121662656666255333255666126663331224444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "284": {
    "question": "3200420024001400003000043010401024062040000000050",
    "answer": "3244422324551435553444443314421224562644456666555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "285": {
    "question": "6000000404401400020202102320120540102006000440001",
    "answer": "6666664444431425523242152324125544142666444446661",
    "size": 7
  },
  "286": {
    "question": "5200300000322000000046522400030100000300400004250",
    "answer": "5223344556322465666646522465633144566342456444255",
    "size": 7
  },
  "287": {
    "question": "0250060026055003040400605040050503001606600500550",
    "answer": "1255666326555633644466665546655533321666662555556",
    "size": 7
  },
  "288": {
    "question": "3100000000401022045060020330002002054040200100604",
    "answer": "3155566334451622445665523336542662454446245166644",
    "size": 7
  },
  "289": {
    "question": "2201006310304605000400020400020002055050635002013",
    "answer": "2251666315334635534463522426226662355556635122613",
    "size": 7
  },
  "290": {
    "question": "1006000033202200001601500002022000005000050300041",
    "answer": "1366666533262255521661566662522555255544555333441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "291": {
    "question": "3203330030000200510216023030012000000040310260030",
    "answer": "3223332335555266512216623332612466264446312266633",
    "size": 7
  },
  "292": {
    "question": "1006000010420102030300240042010500002333101200001",
    "answer": "1666666514422152433325245542515554452333141244441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "293": {
    "question": "1000042030001001500002060004101030020213000100063",
    "answer": "1344442335551221554442666364161636326213632126663",
    "size": 7
  },
  "294": {
    "question": "4440000002036320263005000005003220552206000000215",
    "answer": "4446633242636321263655366365533226552216655512215",
    "size": 7
  },
  "295": {
    "question": "1005000500430000000310300000000056303404103500000",
    "answer": "1445555534433553566315355666554556333444133555553",
    "size": 7
  },
  "296": {
    "question": "0060001505522005000002002204100430034405020002100",
    "answer": "6666661555522425666442662234164433234455523322155",
    "size": 7
  },
  "297": {
    "question": "5001220220000000100630644400050002001300241000010",
    "answer": "5551223225566366166636644464655542461355241332214",
    "size": 7
  },
  "298": {
    "question": "5055200014040400004000230160003000040305500056105",
    "answer": "5555224514446442664644236164453656645365565556155",
    "size": 7
  },
  "299": {
    "question": "0006000020031004221001000020033301300050020030401",
    "answer": "4266666423331644221231555523533351355554223334441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "300": {
    "question": "0220020033000063405030040504500056055455035500000",
    "answer": "6226223633664363465436646544564656355455635566663",
    "size": 7
  },
  "301": {
    "question": "4040020450043005046600500040062104004400320100301",
    "answer": "4441223455443365546646524644662164264466326144331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "302": {
    "question": "0340002000060010013000100100000401010302034020002",
    "answer": "3344442366666216413332144122243421314332334422122",
    "size": 7
  },
  "303": {
    "question": "2600302000100240254350050400455440540060006040041",
    "answer": "2666332262131246254354655435455443546666556644441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "304": {
    "question": "0060000105030402203000000312013002002404035003002",
    "answer": "6666664155534452253425335312513422352444335233322",
    "size": 7
  },
  "305": {
    "question": "5000440051400004001355050503143002000031200120006",
    "answer": "5224445551455554451355455533143352633231263126666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "306": {
    "question": "0200000026033405005160020500413005044406500000010",
    "answer": "5266444526333455665165226566413355644436566666616",
    "size": 7
  },
  "307": {
    "question": "4555003000054306544054000005205233025500001006333",
    "answer": "4555533466654346544454652355265233525566651666333",
    "size": 7
  },
  "308": {
    "question": "1040042360000003201300004305106000040400010105000",
    "answer": "1644442366666233221354444335166655544466614155555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "309": {
    "question": "0103501020310000030201000010005100000060220005004",
    "answer": "3153551325315532532251656616665166656664225555444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "310": {
    "question": "5000502140446202000000030100000002055510642030002",
    "answer": "5555562144446222666645333124566662455516642233322",
    "size": 7
  },
  "311": {
    "question": "2044403150003003002000030400003005006000565056405",
    "answer": "2244433155423633552663635456563345656664565556455",
    "size": 7
  },
  "312": {
    "question": "5600000002213005100006004030004004500400010021020",
    "answer": "5666665562213555166356544635664664566464416221422",
    "size": 7
  },
  "313": {
    "question": "1506000004040102010200004043000004000031203230400",
    "answer": "1566666554446152412235254443355554332331223234444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "314": {
    "question": "0001300010022540300306002030020203050540100004001",
    "answer": "4431333413622546366356662635626263552546155554441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "315": {
    "question": "6140600040055004105160000000214052003500200030444",
    "answer": "6146666644555664155166664433214452323555241335444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "316": {
    "question": "4010000542144000002460000000551000004521320000501",
    "answer": "4416666542144654232465133241551233244521324455551",
    "size": 7
  },
  "317": {
    "question": "0613001023052600040400000000020300032102203004440",
    "answer": "6613521623352662445466445546623344632132263344446",
    "size": 7
  },
  "318": {
    "question": "6050000020505602060100100020040303024040200000305",
    "answer": "6656666625555662666166166225646333524442252133355",
    "size": 7
  },
  "319": {
    "question": "0202050044305001005510414440646006004055300401050",
    "answer": "2242251644335561435516414444646666364655336461555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "320": {
    "question": "0140443001300040031002000001004300300044003360210",
    "answer": "4144443441331346431232644321264334336644433362213",
    "size": 7
  },
  "321": {
    "question": "0100420000220002100000103002106335000400000500003",
    "answer": "4144422424223342155324163552166335366444436555553",
    "size": 7
  },
  "322": {
    "question": "0000130144605050440000413330000004400210041010200",
    "answer": "6666133144665355445555413335542554454215541412254",
    "size": 7
  },
  "323": {
    "question": "5005404601030000451000400060005130000403031041001",
    "answer": "5555444651333464451666455563645136366443631441361",
    "size": 7
  },
  "324": {
    "question": "0100040032210002000101004005462000000400231006120",
    "answer": "3144445332215522666151664445462264344466231666123",
    "size": 7
  },
  "325": {
    "question": "0000101104430003010405400042030405000322011060000",
    "answer": "2244131134433453315445444542533455255322511666666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "326": {
    "question": "1000010012014564000000043000400300000130020100402",
    "answer": "1444415612214564445456643545466354544135524144442",
    "size": 7
  },
  "327": {
    "question": "4442030000003050102000100201005310450005400100034",
    "answer": "4442233466663556162555133251525315452555445153334",
    "size": 7
  },
  "328": {
    "question": "1230603004000005445030000000502544000006006040412",
    "answer": "1233663524356355445635145566522544466666426444412",
    "size": 7
  },
  "329": {
    "question": "1040220504600030002003040402002000300034030440603",
    "answer": "1546226554666635422123541462322446343334634446663",
    "size": 7
  },
  "330": {
    "question": "6000004022003200040000343030303400200344021030100",
    "answer": "6664444622333266444123343331343455244344521434155",
    "size": 7
  },
  "331": {
    "question": "0000010340500200004000324400300305016012060000010",
    "answer": "3355512344545244254563324456363355616312666666216",
    "size": 7
  },
  "332": {
    "question": "0020013000000000034036434001001050020310320120033",
    "answer": "6622513644555364334536434441631555223315322122533",
    "size": 7
  },
  "333": {
    "question": "0010600010510003100221050500000610600020301010030",
    "answer": "2216666315516633155221556566556616656623361612136",
    "size": 7
  },
  "334": {
    "question": "0026020000005401000204030300000013100010051210000",
    "answer": "6226224666655441555244533324455513142513351215555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "335": {
    "question": "0000100004000024065301201010330220004000310225000",
    "answer": "6666151244655324465331221512333223244453314225555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "336": {
    "question": "0200006020031000501000005032136320103002002203001",
    "answer": "3266666323331635551326665532136323133632442263441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "337": {
    "question": "3000103410040000300010234453013004030055003300600",
    "answer": "3334133414445342355514234453413544335555633366666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "338": {
    "question": "0000100100030002130000520053010306000020100400130",
    "answer": "5555155125335352136535522653513366654326134442133",
    "size": 7
  },
  "339": {
    "question": "0260000003000010151000022302010000110000000232400",
    "answer": "2266666333555614151524422332415553113325542232444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "340": {
    "question": "0201002014200005010005005005164010100000005000420",
    "answer": "5221662514226255416665645555164615156664445555422",
    "size": 7
  },
  "341": {
    "question": "4045200502000000030000050126000502056005100301021",
    "answer": "4445226542555656233565653126565552656665163331221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "342": {
    "question": "2060002000000000000000035300641012600002104440100",
    "answer": "2666662243556264353366435326641512666622164444166",
    "size": 7
  },
  "343": {
    "question": "0435005400020555012530000000133301330600013004440",
    "answer": "4435555443321555512535515553133351336666613364444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "344": {
    "question": "0300300300555220600420005000520020462130030060020",
    "answer": "3355333366555222666425555644523323462132336666622",
    "size": 7
  },
  "345": {
    "question": "1060030403013000330402006100000000230350000004103",
    "answer": "1666633463613444334442466152266665233355534444133",
    "size": 7
  },
  "346": {
    "question": "0301033530401003004400230020003340520004330010043",
    "answer": "5351333535441553554455235225523345525554332515443",
    "size": 7
  },
  "347": {
    "question": "0000000001000634044501030022013046002200004050220",
    "answer": "3466666341555634344551435422413546642256664455226",
    "size": 7
  },
  "348": {
    "question": "0000002003400500000134004000600530023303020004002",
    "answer": "4633522463455546545134654423665532323353322344442",
    "size": 7
  },
  "349": {
    "question": "0050200002400021600020400400120600502500005000001",
    "answer": "5555221522444421666622444462126656552565555556661",
    "size": 7
  },
  "350": {
    "question": "3001000002040001201250060010501310310300030005004",
    "answer": "3331455552442551241255666615561313316334435555544",
    "size": 7
  },
  "351": {
    "question": "4300100000530330300000550250000010350250000020035",
    "answer": "4333122444533333355515552253566613356255556623335",
    "size": 7
  },
  "352": {
    "question": "1000403200060420550000220540000610220100035050002",
    "answer": "1444433266663425556646225544666612222163335555522",
    "size": 7
  },
  "353": {
    "question": "4022001541050300305600032500064050050402146004204",
    "answer": "4422661541556354335635632563564256456442146664244",
    "size": 7
  },
  "354": {
    "question": "2030001133046000240410500060550540003204443000606",
    "answer": "2236661133646621244412526666555546633224443666666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "355": {
    "question": "0001005040006553040500530004052040005501336000004",
    "answer": "5551655544466553346556536644652244365551336664444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "356": {
    "question": "0102010000000003055000106004300150002051400104000",
    "answer": "4152214435566443355644156664325155532551453154445",
    "size": 7
  },
  "357": {
    "question": "0002401005140202023000500010004402040341002031000",
    "answer": "3322441325144242523324552316454442643341262231666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "358": {
    "question": "6043255040004000124400000000033420004000601333101",
    "answer": "6443255643324564124456132465633426664442661333161",
    "size": 7
  },
  "359": {
    "question": "0120000502013050055355600030031002303325006000010",
    "answer": "5123355562313556655355666535531252363325236666613",
    "size": 7
  },
  "360": {
    "question": "0005055022404201055026003006402303044022304303000",
    "answer": "6655555622444261555426633536422353644122364333666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "361": {
    "question": "1210233004000300044003450005004410520000600004510",
    "answer": "1212233324466335544653455565244416525555654444515",
    "size": 7
  },
  "362": {
    "question": "0240043520030004220000030500000244000100552300150",
    "answer": "5244443523335354225535433554543244424125552333155",
    "size": 7
  },
  "363": {
    "question": "3040003000006102000504000303000321040300004001600",
    "answer": "3444333346666132655554265333455321645332664551666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "364": {
    "question": "0004300210422044600400003032040201250020300003000",
    "answer": "2444333216422444664445463332546241255624335333443",
    "size": 7
  },
  "365": {
    "question": "0005000032020003101660140330625063000506600006000",
    "answer": "6325556632522663151666144336625463662546625556662",
    "size": 7
  },
  "366": {
    "question": "2200441050000014004050600030505002500000102540041",
    "answer": "2244441555553514444356666635555622525333152544441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "367": {
    "question": "6055010200000000502203050350001334204010000000300",
    "answer": "6655615265666526562253656355361334234414424433341",
    "size": 7
  },
  "368": {
    "question": "4040000400005033000061220344200005404000010000306",
    "answer": "4446666435555633533461225344245555424666614433366",
    "size": 7
  },
  "369": {
    "question": "0060000000422000100000000104043030600002206015004",
    "answer": "6666664444422466166646444164643336665552246515444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "370": {
    "question": "3004002030000004004562000020400000005650500401000",
    "answer": "3444422335555624444562555626456662645655564461556",
    "size": 7
  },
  "371": {
    "question": "0000051622500005506320050300355024000052143500000",
    "answer": "6655551622566265566326656334355624432252143555522",
    "size": 7
  },
  "372": {
    "question": "0100010025404540040004630315000600555055100200060",
    "answer": "4155515425444542542254633315166666555555162266666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "373": {
    "question": "4060133400004000434414044103655550006000034440201",
    "answer": "4666133464334346434414644143655555366666134444221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "374": {
    "question": "5310230000030503150000002060010010002204000000020",
    "answer": "5312235535533553155655522565614416562244666666226",
    "size": 7
  },
  "375": {
    "question": "0045000400001010122063030505303440406000030004400",
    "answer": "4445666455561615122563635555363444436313336664444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "376": {
    "question": "0004102001201000040000000050630004003100360000004",
    "answer": "4444122221221644445666355556634444663133366664444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "377": {
    "question": "3330000002060520201003044455364555130014021224441",
    "answer": "3335555262666526261663644455364555136614221224441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "378": {
    "question": "0200001402641001004500004010120600001000010000405",
    "answer": "2266661442641541264554264415126666521655512444455",
    "size": 7
  },
  "379": {
    "question": "0404433000220060515010500040303550200210003125050",
    "answer": "6444433666221365515516533542353554235214453125555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "380": {
    "question": "4302505000144004000452050602140005004450003022055",
    "answer": "4322555433144544566452255642144565234456553322655",
    "size": 7
  },
  "381": {
    "question": "0140001034063020340440431004100000400015000310302",
    "answer": "3146631334463321346442431664143555434415523313332",
    "size": 7
  },
  "382": {
    "question": "3306000034440000000210500010650202405030240102614",
    "answer": "3366666634442665466216552614653262465336246122614",
    "size": 7
  },
  "383": {
    "question": "0200135420003006052000050200004303003000213350050",
    "answer": "4266135426553546652354655215244333523442213355555",
    "size": 7
  }
}